Guide to the Roy Lisker Papers, 1957 -
Roy Lisker Papers 1957 -
- Old box 20: Complete File Ferment Press Books1986-2000
  - Lightnings Crash Around Thunder Echoing Skies (Box 42)
  - Eleven Matrix Poems (Box 42)
  - Memoir (Box 42)
  - Ferment Press Catalogue of 1994 (Box 42)
- Old box 21: Science, Articles and Notebooks1968-1999
  - Basis Representations Paris, 1969 (Box 43)
  - Conical Surfaces Paris, 1968 (Box 43)
  - Generalized Ordinals Large Format Camera Copy (Box 43)
  - Causal Algebras Typescript of 1985 (Box 43)
  - Non-Linear Algebra 1994 Version, with corrections (Box 43)
  - Graph, Linear Chaos Machine, 1987 (Box 42)
  - Projective Constructs, 1999 (Box ?)
  - Question Theory, 1993 (Box 43)
  - Science, miscellaneous (Box 42)
    (i) Group Structure of Monotonic Functions
    (ii) Pseudo-Representations 1999
    (iii) Representation Spaces 1999
    (iv) Modal Logics 1993
    (v) Semiomorphisms 1988
    (vi) Generalized Infinitesimals 1993
  - Dissonant Functions and Sequences, 1978, 1982, 1999 (Box 43)
  - Intrinsic Derivatives, 1993 (Box ?)
  - Fixed Point Theorems, 1985 (Box 43)
  - Cubical Matrices, 1978 (Box 43)
  - Big Bang Moment, May 1976 (Box ?)
  - Co-Homotopy, 1993 (Box 43)
  - Transfinite Series, 1980 (Box 43)
  - Antigroups, 1978 (Box 43)
  - Generalized Greatest Integer Function, 1983 (Box ?)
  - Dedekind Induction (Box 43)
  - Knowledge Logics, 1984 (Box 43)
  - Bohr Complementarity (Box 43)
  - Inconceivable Numbers (Box 43)
  - Projective Constructs ( Article in Heavy Ion Physics 1999) (Box 43)
  - Chomsky's Linguistics Exposed! 1991 (Box 43)
  - Euclidean Time, Version of 1987 (Box 43)
  - Shrinking Expectations -Various (Box 43)
  - Theoretical Foundations of Foundation Theory Version of 1994 (Box 43)
  - Theoretical Foundations of Foundation Theory Version of 1994 (Box 43)
  - Iterate Sets, Patterned Functions Version of 1984 (Box 43)
  - Generalized Centroids 1980; Polyps 1987; Patterned Forms 1981 (Box 43)
  - Papers on Algebra, 1984 (Box 43)
  - Article on Fermat's Last Theorem, 1995 (Box 43)
  - Alexander Yesenin-Volpin, 1993 (Box 43)
  - "Shepherd's Pi", 1978 (Box ?)
  - List of Potential Science Projects - Handwritten and Typescript (Box ?)
  - Quantum Notes Boulder, Co., 1992 (Box ?)
  - Materials for Ferment article on Quantum Theory, 1995 (Box 43)
- Old box 22: Graphics et. Alia
  boxes 44-45
  1. Folder, Winter, 1995
  2. Circular Tangrams -Originals 1991
  3. Lyric Anthology I, Illustrated Poetry 1992
  4. Donation Cards, Original Worksheets
  Insane Card; Professor Card; Space Alien Card
  Crazy Card; Wandering Scholar; Woodstock Bohemian
  Harvard Psychiatrist Card
  5. Samples of Donation Cards and Calling Cards
  6. Ferment Press Covers
  7. Application materials for Wesleyan graduate program in Music 10/17/97
  8. Documents from France; Reviews of Novel " Je Suis Trop Intelligente, Moi!" 1968-72
  9. Articles 1994-1999
  Employer's Application
  Ferment Ads
  Mathematics Consultant for the Arts
  Sketch for F Press book on Chaos Theory
  Genteel Gibberish ( Wesleyan Writers Conference) 1997
  M.A.D.E. Manifesto ( Large and Small Format)
  Pianowandeljahre Notes
  Letter to Pat Frederick
  Pat's Reply
  Post-Modern Monochord for Jon Barlow
  10. Publicity, General
  11. Ferment Advertising 1995
  12. Copy of Kodaikanal school Yearbook "Eucalyptus" 1952
  13. Catalogues, Monitors, Brochures. etc. 1990's
  14. Cards and Drawings Berkeley, 1984-87
  15. Cards and Drawings
  16. "Live-Objet pour Joan Tower" 1979; Color Xeroxes
  17. Articles
  (a) Journal of Irreproducible Results 1979
  (b) "Smokey" BUNAC Magazine February 1969
  (c) Commonweal Mag Article, R. Alleva Feb. 2001
  18. 'Application for Visiting Scholar' Documents Berkeley 1985
  19. Articles from "The Observer" Bard College 1977-79
- Old box 23: Science, Notebooks
  box 45
  1. Reprint of "Projective Constructs" Article from Heavy Ion Physics, pgs. 49-56. November 2000
  2. Inventory of Science Papers Version of 1997
  3. Project Notebook, December, 2000
  4. Ellis Horwood - Business Correspondence
  5. "Causal Algebras " Original Version, Berkeley 1983-87
  6. "Counter-Intuitive Science" Revision Pages November 2001
  7. "Counter-Intuitive Science" Revision Pages December 2001
  8. "Topological Insights" Revision Pages 3/20/2002
  9. Addresses from the ICMP Conference, Boulder CO 1983
  10. Addresses from the Fractals Conference Cincinnati 1987
  11. Mathematics Notebook August, 2000
  12. Bidirectional Notebook:
  Front: American Mathematical Society, Jan 2000
  Back: Study and Research
  13. Mathematics Manual. Original Handwritten Version
  14. Planning Book for the "Grothendieck Meeting" Paris, February 2001
  15. Ferment Mailing List September 2001
- Old box 24: Ferment
  boxes 46-47
  1. Samples in looseleaf binder 1983
  2. Russell Biography review - 2nd Revision pages
  3. Ferment V: Eiffel Tower Gang, ( complete)
  4. Notes for review "A Beautiful Mind"
  5. Ferment IV Large Format
  6. Russell Biography review - 1st Revision pages
  7. Notes for review of Bertrand Russell biography of Ray Monk
  8. Ferment XV#3 Revision Pages
  9. Ferment XV#3
  10. Ferment XV#3 Third Revision
  11. FermentXV#7 Second Revision
  12. FermentXV#3 Beaver Falls section
  13. Notes for Russell biography review
  14. Ferment XIV#10, #11 Draft Version "Revolution at Pierrefonds”
  15. Ferment XV#3 Tivoli, NY section
  16. Eiffel Tower Gang, Finale
  17. Ferment V #11 Eiffel Tower Gang
  18. New Universe Weekly, November 1981 - Croton on Harmon
  19. Ferment Volume I: Miscellaneous
- Old box 25: Manuscripts, etc.
  boxes 47-48
  1. Governments of Chelm Large Format, 2-sided
  2. Tales of Frustrated Musicians Version of 1997 Small Format
  3. Notes for Essay "Milton and Music" November 2001
  4. Draft of Milton Essay
  5. "State of the Bunion" Editorial February 2002
  6. Tales of Frustrated Musicians Version of 1997 Large Format
  7. "Chronicles of Nin". Reduced format, version May 2001
  8. "Chronicles of Nin". Final Version, January 2002
  9. Novel, "Eiffel Tower Gang" 2nd Revision Loose Sheets
  10. "Eiffel Tower Gang" Final revision, version of Dec. 13, 2001
  11. "Chronicles of Nin" Revision December 13, 2001
  12. The Cannes Festival IT May, 1970
  13. Eiffel Tower Gang - Loose revision sheets
  14. "Amplitude of the Cosmos" Galleys from XLibris
  15. Harvest of Chains, Novel. Revision of Chapter I.
- Old box 26: Journals
  boxes 49-50
  1. Travel Journal, October 2001 St. Louis/Chicago
  2. AMS Conference Jan 17-20, 2000 Washington, DC. Back portion has science study and research.
  3. Mathematics Research "Red Journal" Indexed April 2001
  4. Study of Symplectic Geometry "Green Journal" July 2001
  5. Research Journal December 2000 Indexed
  6. Study and Research May 2002 Indexed
  7. Research Journal February 2002 Indexed
  8. General Journal November 2001
  9. Schedules Notebooks April-October 2002
  10. Winter Folder, March 2000
- Old box 27: Revision sheets
  boxes 50-51
  1. Meal Ticket I, II, III First Revision
  2. Meal Ticket I, II, III Second Revision
  3. Ferment XVI#3 - Third Revision
  4. Draft pages, Brahmagupta I
  5. Brahmagupta I - Second Revision
  6. Mousetrap Tech, essay of 1980, revised for website 2002
  7. New York City Antiwar movement, retranslated and revised from article in "Les Temps Modernes" 1972; put on website August 2002
  8. Notes on the 'Quantum Limits to the Second Law' Conference, University of San Diego, July-August 2002
  9. Ferment XV#7 Jan Mycielski article, updating of Cripple Factor. Intermediate camera copy.
  10. Ferment XV#7 Source materials and background notes
  11. Background articles for review of Russell Biography
  12. FXV#6 Science Catalogue. Revision sheets
  13. Source materials for Ferment XV#3
  14. Brahmagupta I. The First Problem Set October 2002
- Old box 28: Materials for "Problem Books"
  boxes 51-52
  (A.) Computation Notebooks:
  1. September 18th, 2002
  2. Hypatia Problems, January 2003
  3. Sketches 10/29/02
  4. August 24, 2002
  5. November 5,2001
  6. October 2002 - February 2003
  7. January 29, 2003
  (B) Legal Steno Pads: Computations
  (C) Antigroups Paper Oct 12, 2002
  Transcription/ Revision
  Original paper of June, 1978
  (D) Revision for website of:
  Topological Paradoxes of Time Measurement
  (E) Revision sheets for Problem Books:
  1. Brahmagupta II
  2. Hipparchus I Dec 27, 2002
  3. Hipparchus I Sketches January 2003
  4. Vive La Differance I Draft, March 2003
  5. Vive La Differance I Editorial Revision March 2003
  6. Arithmetic Progression Problem Dec 4, 2002
  7. Relativity Problem: Brahma I, Hipparchus I
  8. Ferment Press copies:
  Brahmagupta I
  Brahmagupta II
  Hipparchus I
  Vive I
- Old box 29
  boxes 52-54
  1. Botstein "Pardon " letter, and response
  2. Ainay-le-Chateau Original typescript
  3. Website Film Reviews, March-May 2003
  4. Ferment XVI#7, #11 First revision sheets
  5. Ferment XVI, #4, #5 Second Revision sheets
  6. Ferment XVI # 7 Second Revision Sheets
  7. Ferment XVI#7 Penultimate version
  8. Ferment XVI#8 Final Draft. Editorial Revision
  9. Ferment XVI#6 Penultimate Version
  10. Ferment Mailing List 2002-2003; Reading List, January 2003
  11. Harvest of Chains, Novel. Typescript of 1989
  12. Ferment XVI#11 2nd Revision
  13. Ferment XVI#11 3rd Revision
  14. Ainay-le-Chateau. Revision for website
  15. Schedules Notebook Oct. 9, 02 - May 1, 03
  16. Meal Ticket, Novel: Madhouse episode Ferment XVI#8. First Revision.
  17. Ferment XVI#12 Meal Ticket, Final Chapter, Revisions
  18. Ferment Mailing List January 2003
- Old box 30
  boxes 54-55
  1. Quest of the Absolute, Short Story, Revision 11/2003
  2. MIT Information Desk, Play, Original Mss of 1965
  3. Sam the Messiah Man, Short Story, Performance Script, 2000-2004
  4. Chomsky/Schenker Essay, Revision Pages
  5. Chomsky/Schenker, Second Revision
  6. Editorials from Ferment Magazine.Org, Revisions 11/2004
  7. Rehabilitation, Playscript - 1976 Version
  8. Ferment XVII#5, First Revision
  9. Ferment XVI#12 "Meal Ticket" Finale. Revision Pages
  10. Meal Ticket, Novel. Appendices, Unrevised
  11. Ferment XVII#1 Three Book Reviews: all revisions
  12. Ferment XVII#2 "Shock and Awe" Draft Version
  13. Ferment XVII#3 "Blues for Christian Herman" reprint with editing of Ferment VI 9/13/87
  14. Ferment XVII#3 First Revision
  15. Ferment XVII #8 :"Little Eyolf" Revision Pages
  16. Little Eyolf. Essay September 2004
  17. Little Eyolf: Notes
  18. Little Eyolf: Commentaries
  19. Ferment 2003: Mailing Lists.
- Old box 31
  boxes 55-56
  1. Notes on the Democratic National Convention, July 25-29, 2004
  2. Ferment XVII#5 Second Revision
  3. Ferment XVII#4 "Biodefense" Revision Pages
  4. Time and the Maya. Essay. Original pages, 1963
  5. Quest for Grothendieck -Original typescript. Part I, June 1969
  6. Life and Life Energy. Version 2004. Chap 1 Revision Pages
  7. Life and Life Energy. Version 2004. Chap 2 Revision Pages
  8. Life and Life Energy. Version 2004. Chap 3 Revision Pages
  9. Life and Life Energy. Version 2004. Chap 3 Revision Pages
  10. Life and Life Energy. Version 2004. Chap 3 Revision Pages
  11. Life and Life Energy. Version 2004. Chap 4 Revision Pages
  12. Life and Life Energy. Version 2004. Chap 4 Revision Pages
  13. Associative Harmony. Text. Version of 2004
  14. Vive La Difference II: Emilie du Chatelet: Research, Notes, Revision Pages
- Old box 32
  boxes 56-58
  1. Travel Journal, Summer 2003
  2. Journal, August 2003
  3. Journal, April 3, 2004
  4. Notebooks, Democratic National Convention, Republican National Convention, 2004
  5. Research Notebook for series "Bush/Cheney Assault on Science"
  6. Math Research Notebook, October 2003
  7. Math Studies Notebook, July-December 2004
  8. Research Notebook December 2003
  9. Publication Planning Journal, April 19, 2000
- Old box 33
  boxes 58-59
  1. Notes and various revisions of review of Roger Penrose’s “Road to Reality”
  2. Revision pages: Paris travelogue 2005
  3. Quantum Question Theory paper May 31, 2005
  4. Revision pages for Quantum Question Theory
  5. Einstein Centennial Symposium article, revision of 2005
  6. Revision pages for Einstein Centennial Symposium article
  7. Mathematics Manual, first draft
  8. History of North End Housing Initiative Feb 24, 05
  9. Relativity on 2-Manifolds, revision pages, Feb 22, 05
  10. “College President’s Speech” Editorial, December 2004
  11. Isostructuralism article, revisions December 10, 2004
  12. (a) Restricted Collision Theorem (b) General Collision Theorem (c) Fibre Bundles lecture (d) Trains and Fly (e) Lie Algebras and Lie Groups – December 2005
  13. General Collision Theorem, revision pages December 2004
  14. Non-Metrizable Time. First revision December 7th 2005
  15. Non-Metrizable Time, second revision December 14 05
  16. Non-Metrizable Time, finished article
  17. Sam the Messiah Man, recitation script December 2004
  18. Life and Life Energy 6, revision pages
  19. Story “A Child is Born”, 2 revisions
  20. Arles Travelogue Revision, November 2005
  21. Einstein Centennial Symposium. Draft of lecture notes 10/27/05
  22. Einstein Centennial Symposium, lecture notes Nov-Dec 2005
  23. Review of Penrose “Road to Reality”, prepared for publication by the Mathematical Intelligencer (1st, 2nd and 3rd revisions)
  24. Travel Notes, Montpellier March 23-27 2005
  25. Life and Life Energy 5, revision notes
  26. Aix en Provence travelogue, 2005, first revision
- Old box 34
  boxes 59-60
  (1) Copies of booklets of Ferment Press, first editions
  (2) Letters and Postcards to family 1970-2000+
  (3) “Philadelphia Literary Intelligencer” - Feb 20,1961
  (4) Report Cards
- Old box 35
  box 61
  (1) Boston/Cambridge Notebook, July/August 2005
  (2) Science Notebook 2003
  (3) Planning notebook, travels in France Feb 21, 2005
  (4) Math/Science Notebook Jan 8th 2005
  (5) Provence Notebook March 2, 2005
  (6) Schedules Notebook June 03 – May 04
  (7) Journal, July 2004-August 2005
  (8) Travel Journal Jan 8,2004 – April 14, 2005
- Old box 36
  boxes 62-63
  (1) Harvest of Chains revision pages Chapter 3
  (2) Harvest of Chains revision pages Chapter 2
  (3) Lamentation for Rachel Corrie April 2006
  (4) Rachel Corrie – 1st revision
  (5) Rachel Corrie – 2nd revision
  (6) Rachel Corrie – background materials
  (7) 3 playscript of Hamlet, filled with marginalia
  (8) Photocopy of original Mss of “Getting That Meal Ticket” made by Rene Julliard in 1971
  (9) Harvest of Chains – revision pages, Chapter 7
  (10) Harvest of Chains, Chapter 7th, second revision
  (11) “MIT Information Desk” 1-Act Play, original 1964 typescript
  (12) “Rehabilitation” 4 Act Play, 1st and 2nd revisions
  (13) “Street Musician in France” English typescript of article published in Les Temps Modernes 1970
  (14) Harvest of Chains Chapter 7, 3rd revision
  (15) Kangaroo That Wanted To Sing, Children’s Play Version of 1987
  (16) Commerce and Illusions – Version of 1969, Film Script
  (17) Short, unedited scripts
  (a) Woman of the Mountains, play 1959
  (b) Feedback Box film script 1970
  (18) El Pessebre, incomplete novel 5 Chapters
- Old box 37: Ferment Camera Copies
  boxes 63-65
  (1) Ferment V, reduced
  (2) Ferment IX
  (3) Ferment VII
  (4) Ferment VIII
  (5) Ferment X
  (6) Ferment VI
  Ferment IV #1 (Blues for Christian Hermann)
  Psychotherapy Series XI #8, 9, 10 XII#3
  Miscellaneous Issues, Vols. I to IV
- Old box 38
  boxes 65-67
- Old box 39
  boxes 67-68
  (1) Original Camera Copy “Legends of Broken Hearts”
  Cover, Two Nervous Breakdown Stories
  (2) Photocopies of Stories
  (i) Tales of Frustrated Musicians
  (ii) Cynical Xmas Stories
  (iii) Alienism
  (iv) Syphilization and its Discontents
  (v) Meal Ticket, Chapter 5
  (vi) Revelation of Dr. Snew
  (vii) The Drugstore
  (viii) Parisian Still-Lifes
  (3) Chomsky’s Linguistics Exposed, Camera Copy
  (4) Background Notebook for articles on John Nash
  (5) Photocopies 2: Stories
  (i) Night of the Gluon
  (ii) Bus Paradox
  (iii) Monaco
  (iv) GGR11
  (6) Program of J Basinger Milton Marathon at 3 Rivers College, with notice of reading of “Milton and Music”
  (7) Hungary Summer 1999; Cards and paraphernalia
  (8) Vive La Difference 2: Emilie de Chatelet
  (9) GRG11 article, revision 5/98
  (10) Ferment XIV #10 Pierrefonds, large format
  (11) FermentXIV#11 Pierrefonds 2
  (12) Notebook, Ferment IX March 1995
  (13) Background articles for the Psychotherapy series
  Ferment XI# 8, 10, XII#3
  (14) Background materials for “JS Bach and the Reformation”
- Old box 40
  boxes 69-70
  (1) New Universe Weekly, Vol. II: Camera Copies
  (2) Harvest of Chains, revisions 200607:
  Chapters 4 -6, 8, 9, 11
  (3) Journal Notes December 1, 2002
  (4) Memoir, with correspondence with Carol Lisker August 2006
  (5) Scotland Journals, Notes, Travelogue Episodes, together with abridgement for Russell Library lecture February 24,07
  (6) Duchesse d’ Antan; Episodes 1 -6
  (7) Journals:
  (1) Scotland, August 24-September 8
  (2) Planning Journal
  (8) Texts revised for Upload to Ferment Magazine, Scotland articles
  (9) Set Theory and Form, January 2007 Revision Pages
  (10) Scotland, miscellaneous items
  (11) Finances Pocket Notebook
  (12) Diskettes, Sciences 1997-2004
  (13) Small Journal June 2001-Jan 2002 Includes notes made during the week after the World Trade Center disaster, with a visit to NYC.
- Old box 41
  boxes 70-72
  Documents, tenure as president of the North End Action Team, 1996-2000
- Old box 42
  boxes 72-73
  1. Research Notebook July 20,2006 Indexed
  2. Research Notebook March 20, 2007, working out of material on Double Intersection Geometry
  3. Research Notebook, January 20,2007 Indexed
  4. Journal, September 4, 2005
  5. Schedules May 29,2005 to March 17, 2007
  6. Outlets and Income Notebook Nov 11, 2005-April 2007
  7. Translation Pages of collection of essays by Rene Thom, “Predire N’est Pas Expliquer” Chapters 1, 2, 3
- Old box 43
  boxes 73-75
  (1) Script of Power Point presentation March 2007 at the Russell Library, “Roaming California”
  (2) Harvest of Chains revisions Chapters 1 through 16
  (3) Contents Outline, Ferment Magazine April 30,2007
  (4) Earlier Version “Bohemian Card”
  (5) Notes for talk on trip to France, 2005, Russell Library lecture
  (6) Street Musician in France; Pierrefonds. English language texts of the Temps Modernes articles
  (7) Jan 2003. Scanned sheets of the Matrix Poems for Website
  (8) Sam the Messiah Man Dec 04 version, Dec 07 version
  (9) D.G. Rossetti talk, Buttonwood Tree, September 4,1997
  (10) Drawings, Berkeley 1984-87
  (11) “Kwantum Fyld Thyry” Research, Nov 27,07 Indexed
  (12) Literary workbook Nov 12, 2005 – Indexed
  (13) Various published items:
  “Mismeasurement of Pi” Journal of Irreproducible Results March/April 1998
  (14) Commonweal Interview, Richard Alleva Feb 9,2001
  (15) Address Books
- Old box 44
  boxes 75-76
  (1) Lecture on Projective Constructs, with 3 transparencies, Nyerigyhaza Hungary 1999
  (2) Report on Hungary conference
  (3) Transparencies of report on Hungary conference
  (4) Bus Paradox, satiric essay, upgraded Jan 2004
  (5) “Theoretical Foundations of Foundation Theory” A Study in Meta-Geometry. Large Format
  (6) Vector Fields. Notes for seminar in the Wesleyan Physics Department April 20, 2005
  (7) Theory Seminar April 14, 2006
  (8) Big Bang Moment Festival
  Poster, Booklet and Button May 5 1977
  (9) Shepherds Pi – A collection of mathematics games and puzzles. 1978
  (10) Generalized Ordinals Reduced Version 1981
  (11) Grothendieck Project, Correspondence
  E-Mails
  (12) Galilean Relativity and Inertial Groups Oct 5, 05
  (13) Linear Chaos Machine 1987
  (14) Lecture Notes, for Einstein Centennial Symposium talk October 27, 2005
  (15) Dirac Equation seminar, lecture notes April 13, 2007
  (16) Basis Expansions 1969
  (17) Observations on Conical Geometry 1969
  (18) Talk in Wes Physics Dept Euclidean Time and Relativity
  (19) On Counter-Intuitive Time USD QLSL2 2002
  (20) Lecture Notes “Causal Algebras” WES Student Physics Society 1993
  (21) Non-Linear Algebra, Dynamical Systems I and II
  (22) Quantum Question Theory. Notes
  (23) Projective Constructs and Concepts
  (24) Einstein Centennial Symposium. The original article in Les Temps Modernes
  (25) Dissonant Functions. Number Theory paper
  (26) Associative Harmony IRCAM Talk March 2005
  (27) Paper on Fixed Point Theorems
  (28) Fund Appeal Letter February 2, 2008
  (29) Hamlet’s Psychiatrist, various revisions 2008
  (30) Research Notebook April 13, 2007
- Old box 45
  boxes 76-77
  (1) Some watercolors of Sara Starekow Lisker
  (2) PR Folder March 1995
  (3) Photo Album
  (4) Envelopes of photos, going back to 1970’s
- Old box 46
  boxes 77-78
  (1) December 19, 2008 Editorial 10 of the new series of editorials “Soloists and Lost Geniuses”
  (2) Hysteria and Enlightenment Chapters 1 and 2 Revision pages
  (3) Second revision pages, Chapter 1, Hysteria and Enlightenment
  (4) Omar Khayyam Problem Book
  (a) Original Draft
  (b) First revision
  (c) Second revision
  (5) Revision pages, abridged version of Quest for Grothendieck, July 2008
  (6) Hamlet’s Psychiatrist, corrections March 10, 2008
  (7) Hamlet’s Psychiatrist script, with corrections March 22,08
  (8) Hamlet’s Psychiatrist, more corrections March 2008
  (9) Notes for the Isaac Newton, Great Books seminar at the Russell Library June 2, 2008
  (10) “Ordinal Maps” Ordinal Arithmetic and Dynamic Systems February 5, 2008
  (11) Ordinal Maps, Finished version May 30, 2008
  (12) Hamlet’s Psychiatrist, final proof-reading May 27, 2008
  (13) Planning Sheets, European trop Sept-Oct 2008
  (14) Ordinal Maps Version of May 30, 2008
  (15) Editorial, July 8th 08 Hanging Out at Universities
  (16) Omar Khayyam Problem Book; 3rd Revision November 20th, 2008
  (17) Research Journal, May 2003 Indexed
  (18) First Version of 50 Problems Anthology (“26 Problems”)November 30, 2008
  (19) 50 Problem Anthology 2nd Draft December 7, 2008
  (20) Solution Sets for Problem Anthology Revisions Dec 8, 08
  (21) Schedules, Log Book June 1,03 – May, 05
  (22) Journal Aix en Provence Sept 2008; in reverse direction, Paris Journal, October 2008
  (23) An old address book from 1988
- Old box 47
  boxes 78-79
  (1) Power Point text Russell Library Travelogue Europe Sept07 – January 2008; April 19, 08
  (2) Revisions of PPT text of Travelogue
  (3) Copy of translation of essays of Rene Thom “Predire n’est pas Expliquer” 2008
  (4) Proof reading of travelogue for upload to Ferment Magazine
  (5) Editing Travelogue text
  (6) Travel Notes compiled from E-Mail messages
  (7) Travelogue Draft 1, Part 1
  (8) Editorial April 6, 2008 “Manipulating the 2-Party System”
  (9) Editing Power Point of Travelogue March 25
  (10) Journal, Travel Summer 2007
  (11) Poetry, “Kaleidoscope: Chapbook 1987
  (12) Early Poetry 1958-60
  (13) Miscellaneous Poetry Sketches
  (14) Editorial, French writers of the 30’s
  (15) Lamentation for Rachel Corrie June 26, 2008
  (16) “Checkmarks,” European Notebook Sept 07-Jan 09
  (17) “Ideas” Journal from the Poincare Institute October 15,07
- Old box 48
  boxes 79-80
  (1) Math Research Computation Book, subtitled “Relativity for the General Public” January 2005 section; February 2009 section. Indexed
  (2) Mesmer/Marie-Therese von Paradis (MMT) 8: “The Music Lesson” 4 revisions
  (3) MMT 7 “The Dream Sonata” Copies and Revisions
  (4) Editorials and Statistics, February 2009
  (5) Miscellaneous Papers, 2004
  (6) MMT 9 :”The Royal Astronomer”, revisions 1 and 3
  (7) “El Pessebre”, Chapter 2, revision pages and old outlines
  (8) Mathematics Research Journal October 2004 Indexed
  (9) Schedules Journal
  (a) June 2006: Planning Scotland journey
  (b) March 2007-April 2009
  (10) Gallery of Photographs ages 2-70. Package sent by sister, Carol Kennedy, on December 8th